Guide to the Chard Powers Smith Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1901-1978; Series I; 21.27; (51 boxes)
  - General Correspondence, 1910-1978
    - Pinckney, Josephine, 1945-1953 (Box 27, Folder 1142)
    - Piney Woods School, 1972 July 28 (Box 27, Folder 1143)
    - Piper, Jon, 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1144)
    - Piper, Miriam S., 1967-1974 (Box 27, Folder 1145)
    - Pistorus, G., 1970 July 27 (Box 27, Folder 1146)
    - The Players, 1939-1941 (Box 27, Folder 1147)
    - Pledge for Peace Committee, 1944 August 22 (Box 27, Folder 1148)
    - Plumb Memorial Library; Shelton (Conn.), 1942 November 4 (Box 27, Folder 1149)
    - Pocket Books, Inc., 1959, undated (Box 28, Folder 1150)
    - Poetry Society of America, 1966-1973 (Box 28, Folder 1151)
      See also: Davidson, Gustav
    - Poetry a Magazine of Verse
    - Post, Alice Hyde, 1941 (Box 28, Folder 1152)
    - Post, Chandler R., 1924 March 31 (Box 28, Folder 1153)
    - Post Publishing Co., 1951 (Box 28, Folder 1154)
    - Potter, Grace, 1929 April 15 (Box 28, Folder 1155)
    - Potter, Russell and Dean, 1932-1960 (Box 28, Folder 1156-1157)
    - Pottle, Rockwell, 1943 October 21 (Box 28, Folder 1158)
    - Powers, Anne, 1928-1944 (Box 28, Folder 1159-1160)
    - Powers, George G., 1940 (Box 28, Folder 1161)
    - Powers, W. T., 1942 June 30 (Box 28, Folder 1162)
    - Prairie Schooner, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 1163)
    - Prentice, Dody and Merrill, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1164)
    - Prentice, Frank, 1935 November 27 (Box 28, Folder 1165)
    - Prentice, W., 1944 July 23 (Box 28, Folder 1166)
    - The Press of Western Reserve University, 1957 may 1 (Box 28, Folder 1167)
    - Preston, Kendall, 1935 March 19 (Box 28, Folder 1168)
    - Princeton University Library, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1169)
    - Priestly, J. B., 1948 (Box 28, Folder 1170)
    - Proctor, William Ross, 1940 January 30 (Box 28, Folder 1171)
    - Progoff, Ira, 1962 May 5 (Box 28, Folder 1172)
    - Prud'Homme, Hector, 1960-1968 (Box 28, Folder 1173)
    - Pulsifer, Harold T., 1935-1936 (Box 28, Folder 1174)
    - Purves, Austin Jr., 1949 June 22 (Box 28, Folder 1175)
    - Putnam, John C., 1966 (Box 28, Folder 1176)
    - Putney School, 1948-1969 (Box 28, Folder 1177)
    - Pye, John William, 1975 August 21 (Box 28, Folder 1178)
    - Pynson Printers Inc., 1935 (Box 28, Folder 1179)
    - "R" General, 1953-1973 (Box 28, Folder 1180)
    - Radcliffe Quarterly, 1964 August 17 (Box 28, Folder 1181)
    - Ramanujan, Dr. A. K. and Molly, 1948-1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 1182-1183)
    - Ranck, Carty, 1935 (Box 28, Folder 1184)
    - Random House, Inc., 1949-1956 (Box 28, Folder 1185)
    - Ransom, John Crow, 1960 November 2 (Box 28, Folder 1186)
    - Raymond, Dora Neil, 1936 (Box 28, Folder 1187)
    - Raymond, Thoreau E., 1972 June 17 (Box 28, Folder 1188)
    - Read, Bria, undated (Box 28, Folder 1189)
    - Read, Gardner and Vail, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 1190)
    - Read, Jean C., 1924 (Box 28, Folder 1191)
    - Recchia, Kitty, 1960-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 1192-1193)
    - Reed, Caroline, 1968 July 22 (Box 29, Folder 1194)
    - Reed College, 1948 June 22 (Box 29, Folder 1195)
    - Reed, George S., 1940 July 29 (Box 29, Folder 1196)
    - The Reviewer, 1925 January 28 (Box 29, Folder 1197)
    - Reynard, Grant, 1935 May 13 (Box 29, Folder 1198)
    - Rhoads, William, 1964, undated (Box 29, Folder 1199)
    - Rice, Frederick, 1930 September 18 (Box 29, Folder 1200)
    - Rich, Townsend and Jean, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1201)
    - Richards, Archie M., 1975 November 20 (Box 29, Folder 1202)
    - Richards, Edward A., 1962 February 11 (Box 29, Folder 1203)
    - Richards, John, 1964-1966 (Box 29, Folder 1204)
    - Richards, Laura, 1935-1936 (Box 29, Folder 1205)
    - Richards, Rosalind, 1962-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1206)
    - Richardson, Nina Maude, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 1207)
    - Ricks, Arnold and Pat, undated (Box 29, Folder 1208)
    - Riis, Roger William, 1942 September 8 (Box 29, Folder 1209)
    - Riley, Elizabeth, 1951 October 22 (Box 29, Folder 1210)
    - Rinehart & Company, 1946-1958 (Box 29, Folder 1211)
    - Robert M. McBride & Company, 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 1212-1213)
    - Robert M. Weldon Law Offices, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 1214)
    - Roberts, J. Howard, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 1215)
    - Robertson, Allan and Martja, 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1216)
    - Robertson, Archie, 1956 July 3 (Box 29, Folder 1217)
    - Robertson, Ian and Jane, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1218)
    - Robins, Frances, 1928, undated (Box 29, Folder 1219)
    - Robinson, E. A., 1925-1934 (Box 29, Folder 1220-1221)
    - Robinson, Barclay, 1935 November 2 (Box 30, Folder 1222)
    - Robinson, Franchesca B., 1946 June 26 (Box 30, Folder 1223)
    - Robinson, Henry, undated (Box 30, Folder 1224)
    - Robinson, Kelly, 1972, undated (Box 30, Folder 1225)
    - Robinson, Peggy, undated (Box 30, Folder 1226)
    - Robinson, Ray M., 1939 November 2 (Box 30, Folder 1227)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 1228)
    - Rodgers, John, 1951 December 10 (Box 30, Folder 1229)
    - Rodris, Horst, 1973 October 9 (Box 30, Folder 1230)
    - Rogers, C. Thomas, 1968-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1231)
    - Rogers, Francis, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1232)
    - Rogers, Helen Rochester, 1923-1930 (Box 30, Folder 1233-1234)
    - Rogers, Rock R., 1968-1970 (Box 30, Folder 1235)
    - Rollins College, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 1236)
    - Ronsheim, Robert, 1955 May 23 (Box 30, Folder 1237)
    - Roosa, Charles C., 1942 July (Box 30, Folder 1238)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1935-1936 (Box 30, Folder 1239)
    - Roper, Geoff, 1954 August 18 (Box 30, Folder 1240)
    - Roraback, J. Clinton, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1241)
    - Rorke, R. C., 1970 June 5 (Box 30, Folder 1242)
    - Rorty, James and Winifred, 1926-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1243-1249)
    - Rosenberry, Lois, 1948 July 19 (Box 31, Folder 1250)
    - Ross, Frances J., 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1251)
    - The Roswell P. Flower Memorial Library, 1940 February 15 (Box 31, Folder 1252)
    - Ross, Nancy Wilson, 1969 March 23 (Box 31, Folder 1253)
    - Ross, Patricia, 1927 June 16 (Box 31, Folder 1254)
    - Rotary Club, Great Barrington (Mass.), 1955 April 12 (Box 31, Folder 1255)
    - Rotundo, Barbara, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1256)
    - Rous, Peyton, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 1257)
    - Rowland, S. A., 1930 January 2 (Box 31, Folder 1258)
    - Rowley, William, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 1259)
    - Rudd, Alexander Holley, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 1260)
    - Rundlett, Harold, 1956-1957 (Box 31, Folder 1261)
    - Rushton, Marion, 1929 March 2 (Box 31, Folder 1262)
    - Russ, Elmo, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 1263)
    - Russell, Jack, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 1264)
    - Russell and Volkening, Inc., 1945-1965 (Box 31, Folder 1265)
    - Russell Sage College, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 1266)
    - Rutgers University Press, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 1267)
    - "S" General, 1950-1966 (Box 31, Folder 1268)
    - S----, Heide R., 1939 November 30 (Box 31, Folder 1269)
    - Sacket Harbor Lodge No. 135, 1925 November 12 (Box 31, Folder 1270)
    - St. John's Preparatory School, 1932 October 27 (Box 31, Folder 1271)
    - St. Mark's Church In-the-Bowery, 1926 (Box 31, Folder 1272)
    - The St. Nicolas Magazine, 1928 April 13 (Box 31, Folder 1273)
    - Saito, Yamakiko, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 1274)
    - Salerno, Anne, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 1275)
    - Salerno, George and Cindy, 1960-1966 (Box 31, Folder 1276)
    - Salinger, Herman, undated (Box 31, Folder 1277)
    - Salmon, Evelyn, 1940 February 23 (Box 31, Folder 1278)
    - Salter, Katharine Hayden, 1935 April 20 (Box 31, Folder 1279)
    - Saminsky, Lazare, 1941-1954 (Box 31, Folder 1280)
    - Sammpson, Harnet, 1939-1940 (Box 31, Folder 1281)
    - Samuel Scoville Associates, undated (Box 31, Folder 1282)
    - Sanders, Morris, 1956-1959 (Box 31, Folder 1283)
    - Sanderson, Bennett, 1936 September 17 (Box 31, Folder 1284)
    - Sanderson, Caroline, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1285)
    - Sarah Lawrence College, 1949-1950 (Box 31, Folder 1286)
    - Satterfield, J. W., 1940 February 14 (Box 31, Folder 1287)
    - Saturday Review, 1949-1974 (Box 31, Folder 1288)
      See also: Cousins, Norman
    - Savacool, John, 1959-1963 (Box 31, Folder 1289)
    - Sawn, William J., 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1290)
    - Saxon, Lyle, 1929 January 4 (Box 31, Folder 1291)
    - Sayre, Ann Hamilton, 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 1292)
    - Schafer, Gertrude P.
    - Schafer, John C., 1963 July 17 (Box 31, Folder 1293)
    - Schaffner, John, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 1294)
    - Schelling, Helen, undated (Box 31, Folder 1295)
    - Schmitt, Howard G., 1935-1965 (Box 31, Folder 1296)
    - Schneider, Herbert, 1955-1960 (Box 31, Folder 1297)
    - Schulze, Lucy M., 1944-1965 (Box 31, Folder 1298)
    - Schurman, Thomas, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 1299)
    - Schuyler, Daniel, 1938-1942 (Box 31, Folder 1300)
    - Schwab, Arnold T., 1972-1980 (Box 31, Folder 1301)
    - Scott, -----, 1945 (Box 31, Folder 1302)
    - Scott, Al and Charlie, 1941 March 30 (Box 31, Folder 1303)
    - Scott, Charles Henry, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 1304)
    - Scott, Edith and Byron, undated (Box 31, Folder 1305)
    - Scott, Sally, 1959 July 9 (Box 31, Folder 1306)
    - Scott, Ursula, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 1307)
    - Scott, William E., 1941 July 29 (Box 31, Folder 1308)
    - Scott, William T. Jr., 1953 April 1 (Box 31, Folder 1309)
    - Scott, Winifred, 1951-1968 (Box 31, Folder 1310)
    - Scoville, Louise Armstrong, 1943 March 1 (Box 31, Folder 1311)
    - The Scoville Memorial Library, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 1312)
    - The Scribner Bookstore, 1940-1944 (Box 31, Folder 1313)
    - Sedgwick, Sarah, undated (Box 32, Folder 1314)
    - Sedgwick, Volney M., 1937-1952 (Box 32, Folder 1315)
    - Senecal, James Neil, 1910-1940 (Box 32, Folder 1316)
    - Seton, Anya, 1958 April 9 (Box 32, Folder 1317)
    - Seven Gables Book Shop, 1964 March 3 (Box 32, Folder 1318)
    - Sewanee Review, 1961 February 13 (Box 32, Folder 1319)
    - Sexsmith, J. R., 1935, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 1320)
    - Seymour Public Library, 1942 November 23 (Box 32, Folder 1321)
    - Sharnson, Albers, 1927 December 7 (Box 32, Folder 1322)
    - Shaw, Robert, 1965 August 16 (Box 32, Folder 1323)
    - Shearer, Harold and Winifred, 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 1324)
    - Sheffield, Edith, 1971, undated (Box 32, Folder 1325)
    - Sheffield Free Town Library, 1942-1944 (Box 32, Folder 1326)
    - Sheffield, Judy and Alfred, 1968 November 15 (Box 32, Folder 1327)
    - Shelby, C. Levy, 1935 (Box 32, Folder 1328)
    - Shepard, Douglas H., 1953-1955 (Box 32, Folder 1329)
    - Shepard, Odell, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 1330)
    - Sherer, Adelaide, 1947 February 19 (Box 32, Folder 1331)
    - Sherwood, May, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 1332)
    - Shirley, A., 1936 June 21 (Box 32, Folder 1333)
    - Sieverts, Helmut and Celia, 1967-1974 (Box 32, Folder 1334)
    - Siff, Phil, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 1335)
    - Sillee, Leon M., 1939 May 13 (Box 32, Folder 1336)
    - Simison, Barbara Damon, 1952 March 2 (Box 32, Folder 1337)
    - Simmons, R. Wilbur and Nell, 1941, undated (Box 32, Folder 1338)
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1945-1957 (Box 32, Folder 1339)
    - Simpson, Louis M., 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 1340)
    - Sipprell, Clara E., 1971 (Box 32, Folder 1341)
    - Skiff, Frederick Woodword, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 1342)
    - Skiff, Leonard, 1937, undated (Box 32, Folder 1343)
    - Skipp, Frank, 1960-1962 (Box 32, Folder 1344)
    - Slonin, Marc
    - Small, Ruth, 1960 November 26 (Box 32, Folder 1345)
    - Smith, A. Powers, 1923 July 18 (Box 32, Folder 1346)
    - Smith, Cecil, 1946 March 26 (Box 32, Folder 1347)
    - Smith College, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 1348)
    - Smith, F. Gordon, 1948 June 22 (Box 32, Folder 1349)
    - Smith, George and Sydney, 1965-1968 (Box 32, Folder 1350)
    - Smith, Gertrude Robinson, 1951 April 10 (Box 32, Folder 1351)
    - Smith, Glenn E., 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 1352)
    - Smith, H. Allen, 1950 (Box 32, Folder 1353)
    - Smith, Ione, 1956 June 4 (Box 32, Folder 1354)
    - Smith, James Calvert, 1942 December 14 (Box 32, Folder 1355)
    - Smith, Marion and Bradley, 1953-1968, undated (Box 32, Folder 1356)
    - Smith, S. Archibald, 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 1357)
    - Smith, William Warren
    - Smith, Z. V., undated (Box 32, Folder 1358)
    - Snyder, Margaret, 1974 September 17 (Box 32, Folder 1359)
    - Society for the Prevention of World War III, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 1360)
    - Society of American Historians, Inc., 1950 may 11 (Box 32, Folder 1361)
    - Soley, Beth, undated (Box 32, Folder 1362)
    - Somers, Alice, 1965 December 17 (Box 32, Folder 1363)
    - Somont, Marc, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 1364)
    - The South Atlantic Quarterly, 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 1365)
    - Southern Music Publishing Company, Inc., 1950 November 6 (Box 32, Folder 1366)
    - Sparhawk-Jones, Elizabeth, 1935-1936, undated (Box 32, Folder 1367)
    - Spears, Woodbridge, 1967 March 4 (Box 32, Folder 1368)
    - Spencer, Abbot K., 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 1369)
    - Spencer, Duncan M., 1936-1939 (Box 32, Folder 1370)
    - Spencer, Lillian White, 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 1371)
    - Speyer, Leonora, 1928-1935 (Box 32, Folder 1372)
    - Spingarn, Mrs. Joel E., 1935-1946 (Box 32, Folder 1373)
    - The Spiral Press, 1934-1935 (Box 32, Folder 1374)
    - Squires, Alden W., 1939 November 19 (Box 32, Folder 1375)
    - Stacy, Gladys, undated (Box 33, Folder 1376)
    - Stafford, Jack and Sally, 1941 July 30 (Box 33, Folder 1377)
    - Stafford, M. E., 1926 September 20 (Box 33, Folder 1378)
    - Stafford, Robert T. (Senator), 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1379)
    - Stanley, Harry and Helen, 1964-1974 (Box 33, Folder 1380)
    - Stanford University Press, 1956 April 23 (Box 33, Folder 1381)
    - Stanley, ----, 1927 October 31 (Box 33, Folder 1382)
    - Stanley, Gilbert, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 1383)
    - State University of Iowa, 1960 October 21 (Box 33, Folder 1384)
    - Stebbins, Jean, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 1385)
    - Steese, Edward, 1942 March 11 (Box 33, Folder 1386)
    - Steinheart, Dr., 1971 July 24 (Box 33, Folder 1387)
    - Stephen Green Press, 1965-1973 (Box 33, Folder 1388)
    - Stern, Herbert M., 1936, undated (Box 33, Folder 1389)
    - Stevens, Henry H., 1924-1942 (Box 33, Folder 1390)
    - Stewart, ----, 1961 (Box 33, Folder 1391)
    - Stewart, Donald Ogden, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 1392)
    - Stice, Hilda Rose, 1935 June 19 (Box 33, Folder 1393)
    - Stiles, Dan, 1947 January 2 (Box 33, Folder 1394)
    - Stillman, Chauncey, 1942 May 20 (Box 33, Folder 1395)
    - The Stinehour Press, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1396)
    - Stiver, Mary W., 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 1397)
    - Stockbridge Library Association, 1942-1948 (Box 33, Folder 1398)
    - Stoddard, Mary Hoyt, 1946 September 24 (Box 33, Folder 1399)
    - Stokes, David, undated (Box 33, Folder 1400)
    - Stone Church, 1951 November 28 (Box 33, Folder 1401)
    - Stone, Geoffrey, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 1402)
    - Stone, P. M., 1939 November 13 (Box 33, Folder 1403)
    - Stonehill, Mary, undated (Box 33, Folder 1404)
    - Stoney, Louisa Chevis, 1939-1939 (Box 33, Folder 1405)
    - Stork, Charles Wharton, undated (Box 33, Folder 1406)
    - Stoughton, Philip, 1947-1973 (Box 33, Folder 1407)
    - Stout, Rex, 1944 (Box 33, Folder 1408)
    - Strachan, Pearl, 1942-1965 (Box 33, Folder 1409)
    - Strasburger, S. M. Jr., 1940 July 17 (Box 33, Folder 1410)
    - Stratford Library Association, 1942 November 7 (Box 33, Folder 1411)
    - Strode, Hudson, undated (Box 33, Folder 1412)
    - Stuart, Edward T., 1934 (Box 33, Folder 1413)
    - Studman, Marguerite, 1934 February 19 (Box 33, Folder 1414)
    - Stuhlmann, Gunther, 1963-1973 (Box 33, Folder 1415)
    - Sturgis, Mrs. Cyrus C., 1940 November 19 (Box 33, Folder 1416)
    - Sturt, Alfred C., 1936 September 22 (Box 33, Folder 1417)
    - Sudlow, Robert E., 1958-1960 (Box 33, Folder 1418)
    - Sullivan, A. M., 1939-1973 (Box 33, Folder 1419)
    - Sumner, Cid, 1960, undated (Box 33, Folder 1420)
    - Sureda, Eleanor, 1957-1967, undated (Box 33, Folder 1421)
    - Sutcliffe, W. Denham, 1936-1962 (Box 33, Folder 1422)
    - Sutton, Charles T., 1946 February 21 (Box 33, Folder 1423)
    - Swiany, Suzy T., 1974 October 27 (Box 33, Folder 1424)
    - Swift, M. A. R., undated (Box 33, Folder 1425)
    - Swiggett, Howard, 1951 July 31 (Box 33, Folder 1426)
    - Sykes, Marjorie, 1971 March 7 (Box 33, Folder 1427)
    - Syracuse University, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 1428)
    - The Syrian World, 1935 (Box 33, Folder 1429)
    - Szold-Fritz, Bernardine, 1927-1972 (Box 34, Folder 1430-1436)
    - "T" General, 1967-1969, undated (Box 34, Folder 1437)
    - T----, John, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 1438)
    - Taggard, G., 1934 (Box 34, Folder 1439)
    - Taggart, B. B., 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 1440)
    - Talbot, George, 1941-1942 (Box 34, Folder 1441)
    - Talcott, Dudley, undated (Box 34, Folder 1442)
    - Tate, Allen, 1936-1939 (Box 34, Folder 1443)
    - Tatham, Sarah R., 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 1444)
    - Taylor, Fred, 1910-1911 (Box 34, Folder 1445-1446)
    - Taylor Library, Milford (Conn.), 1943 (Box 34, Folder 1447)
    - Taylor, Prentiss, 1929-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1448-1449)
    - Taylor, Roswell Flower, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 1450)
    - Teucar, Lisa, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 1451)
    - Thatcher, Blanche W., undated (Box 34, Folder 1452)
    - Thesis One, 1970-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1453)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company, 1961-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1454)
    - Thomas Nelson & Sons, 1950-1963 (Box 34, Folder 1455-1456)
    - Thomas, Rosemary, 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 1457)
    - Thompson, Mrs. E. R., 1941 (Box 34, Folder 1458)
    - Thompson, Lawrence, 1961-1963 (Box 34, Folder 1459)
    - Thompson, Martha, 1928-1931 (Box 35, Folder 1460-1462)
    - Thompson, Eloise E., 1942-1943 (Box 35, Folder 1463)
    - Thorpe, Marjorie, 1966-1974 (Box 35, Folder 1464)
    - Thurber, Helen, 1944-1949 (Box 35, Folder 1465)
    - Thurber, James, 1945-1957 (Box 35, Folder 1466)
    - Time, Inc., 1964 July 22 (Box 35, Folder 1467)
    - Todrin, Boris, 1948-1965 (Box 35, Folder 1468)
    - Tom Whalen Attorney General Committee, 1967 October 2 (Box 35, Folder 1469)
    - Tomorrow, 1950 (Box 35, Folder 1470)
    - Torrence, Ridgely, 1929-1946 (Box 35, Folder 1471)
    - Torrington Library, Torrington (Conn.), 1943 March 3 (Box 35, Folder 1472)
    - Town & Country Review, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 1473)
    - The Town Hall Club, 1951 March 25 (Box 35, Folder 1474)
    - Trachte, Don, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1475)
    - Tracy, Ruth W., 1946 July 30 (Box 35, Folder 1476)
    - Train, Arthur, 1941 (Box 35, Folder 1477)
    - Travel Bureau, 1929 February 8 (Box 35, Folder 1478)
    - Trexler, H. A., 1950 (Box 35, Folder 1479)
    - Trigg, Emma Gray, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 1480)
    - Trilling, Lionel, 1965-1967 (Box 35, Folder 1481)
    - Trinity College, 1949-1953 (Box 35, Folder 1482)
      See also: Jasmine, Paul
    - Triton Syndicate, Inc., 1935 (Box 35, Folder 1483)
    - Trumbull, Alice, undated (Box 35, Folder 1484)
    - Trumbull, Andrew, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 1485)
    - Tubbs, Henry, undated (Box 35, Folder 1486)
    - Tucker, Mary, 1927-1928 (Box 35, Folder 1487)
    - Tunstal, Mrs. Robert, 1935-1936 (Box 35, Folder 1488)
    - Turner, Nancy, 1928-1965 (Box 35, Folder 1489)
    - Twinem, Leonard, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 1490)
    - Ujanen, Jack, 1933 December 20 (Box 36, Folder 1491)
    - Ulrich, Charles N., 1948 January 13 (Box 36, Folder 1492)
    - Unesco, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 1493)
    - Union Theological Seminars, 1945 (Box 36, Folder 1494)
    - United States. Adjutant General, undated (Box 36, Folder 1495)
    - United States. Consular Service, 1924 December 18 (Box 36, Folder 1496)
    - United States. Department of State, 1960 May 7 (Box 36, Folder 1497)
    - United States. Dept. of the Treasury, 1945 December 20 (Box 36, Folder 1498)
    - United States. Marine Corps, 1953 October 14 (Box 36, Folder 1499)
    - United States. Superintendant of Documents, 1948-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1500)
    - United States. War Dept., 1941-1943 (Box 36, Folder 1501)
    - University Club, 1923-1951 (Box 36, Folder 1502)
    - University of Arkansas Library, 1963 February 11 (Box 36, Folder 1503)
    - University of Buffalo, 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 1504)
    - University of Chicago Press, 1960-1963 (Box 36, Folder 1505)
    - University of Connecticut, 1949-4950 (Box 36, Folder 1506)
    - University of Illinois Press, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1507)
    - University of Iowa Press, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1508)
    - University of Kansas City, 1950-1951 (Box 36, Folder 1509)
    - University of Missouri, 1934 August 17 (Box 36, Folder 1510)
    - University of Nebraska Press, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1511)
    - University of New Mexico Press, 1957 (Box 36, Folder 1512)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1513)
    - University of Redlands, 1956-1957 (Box 36, Folder 1514)
    - University of Vermont, 1934-1971 (Box 36, Folder 1515)
    - Untermeyer, Jean, 1942-1944 (Box 36, Folder 1516)
    - Uphani, Florence, undated (Box 36, Folder 1517)
    - "V" General, 1959-1970 (Box 36, Folder 1518)
    - Valentine, Charles W., 1935 October 2 (Box 36, Folder 1519)
    - Van Arium, Ivan, 1958-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1520)
    - Van Doren, Carl, 1936-1938 (Box 36, Folder 1521)
    - Van Doren, Irita, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 1522)
    - Van Doren, Mark and Dorothy, 1930-1969 (Box 36, Folder 1523-1527)
    - Van Everen, Jay, 1926 (Box 36, Folder 1528)
    - Van Nosdall, George A., undated (Box 36, Folder 1529)
    - Van Soelen, Theodore (Solie), 1940-1960 (Box 36, Folder 1530-1531)
    - Van Santvoord, George, 1952 april 22 (Box 36, Folder 1532)
    - Vansteenburgh, Watson R., 1965 (Box 37, Folder 1533)
    - Vassar College, 1936 January 14 (Box 37, Folder 1534)
    - Vaughn, Rollei, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 1535)
    - Vermont Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1966-1973 (Box 37, Folder 1536)
    - Vermont Bank and Trust Company, 1971 June 17 (Box 37, Folder 1537)
    - Vermont Historical Society, 1967 October 5 (Box 37, Folder 1538)
    - Vermont. Probate Court, 1959 November 24 (Box 37, Folder 1539)
    - Viereck, Peter, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 1540)
    - The Viking Press, 1950-1969 (Box 37, Folder 1541)
    - Vining, Elizabeth Hay, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 1542)
    - Virginia Quarterly Review, 1961-1962 (Box 37, Folder 1543)
    - Voices, 1925 (Box 37, Folder 1544)
    - Vonbehr, Atelier, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 1545)
    - Voza, Phillip, 1943 October 9 (Box 37, Folder 1546)
    - "W" General, 1940-1971 (Box 37, Folder 1547)
    - W. & G. Foyle Ltd., 1955 April 5 (Box 37, Folder 1548)
    - W.W. Norton & Company, Inc., 1958 May 15 (Box 37, Folder 1549)
    - Wagner, Charles, undated (Box 37, Folder 1550)
    - Wagner College, 1949 May 22 (Box 37, Folder 1551)
    - Wagner, Richard S., 1936 may 7 (Box 37, Folder 1552)
    - Wagoner, David, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 1553)
    - Wagstaff, Blanduf, 1935 October 25 (Box 37, Folder 1554)
    - Wald, Max, 1927-1941 (Box 37, Folder 1555-1556)
    - Waldeman, Milton, 1927-1930 (Box 37, Folder 1557)
    - Waldo, George C., 1942 December 16 (Box 37, Folder 1558)
    - Wales, James Albert, 1943 March 26 (Box 37, Folder 1559)
    - Walker, C. Lester, 1945-1972 (Box 37, Folder 1560)
    - Walker, Helen, 1966-1972 (Box 37, Folder 1561)
    - Wallach, Gert, 1954-1973, undated (Box 37, Folder 1562)
    - Walter, George P., 1950 March 17 (Box 37, Folder 1563)
    - Walters, Anne, 1956-1960 (Box 37, Folder 1564)
    - Warden, Nellie C., 1942 October 27 (Box 37, Folder 1565)
    - Warfel, H. R., 1949 (Box 37, Folder 1566)
    - Warfield, Paul, 1963-1965, undated (Box 37, Folder 1567)
    - Waring, Arthur and Eileen, 1965-1973 (Box 37, Folder 1568)
    - Washburn, Carolyn, 1949 July 20 (Box 37, Folder 1569)
    - The Waterbury Hospital, 1953 August 17 (Box 37, Folder 1570)